Who do you count as your friends?
你把谁看作自己的朋友？
From our BFF to a work mate, it’s good to have someone to chew the fat with or offer comfort and support.
从最好的挚友到职场同事，身边能有个人聊聊天、给予安慰和支持，总归是件好事。
But when it comes to friendship, is it more important to have quantity or quality?
但说到友谊，到底是数量重要，还是质量更重要呢？
The recent isolation we have endured due to the coronavirus pandemic has made some of us question our friendships.
新冠疫情让我们经历了一段与世隔绝的时光，这也让有些人开始重新审视自己的友谊。
We’ve fallen out of touch with friends and acquaintances, and it may feel awkward, but do we actually have to rekindle every relationship we once had?
我们与一些朋友和熟人渐渐失去了联系，或许再联系时会感到尴尬，但我们真的有必要重拾每一段过去的关系吗？
It might be time to take stock and think about who you kept in touch with, who you missed talking to, and who you didn’t.
或许是时候好好审视一番，想想疫情期间你一直保持联系的人是谁，想念的聊天对象是谁，而那些你完全不想联系的又是谁。
In short, maybe it’s time to reset your list of real mates.
简而言之，或许是时候重新整理你真正的朋友清单了。
There’s no obligation to stay friends, and writing for BBC Worklife, Bryan Lufkin says: “While people have known for years that friendships are unquestionably good for your health, experts say it’s only natural for acquaintances and even friends to fall by the wayside as time goes on – and it’s nothing to feel guilty about.”
维持友谊并非一种义务，布莱恩·勒夫金在为BBC职场生活频道撰稿时表示：“尽管人们很早就知道，友谊对健康的益处毋庸置疑，但专家称，随着时间流逝，一些熟人甚至朋友逐渐疏远是很自然的事——对此完全不必感到羞愧。”
Of course, it can be hard to choose who’s in your friendship circle.
当然，筛选自己的朋友圈并非易事。
This is what Suzanne Degges-White, professor of counselling at Northern Illinois University, calls our ‘friendscape’.
北伊利诺伊大学的心理咨询学教授苏珊娜·德格斯-怀特将其称为我们的“人际圈”。
She says, “in life, as we go through certain stages and ages, our attention shifts, and we want to be around people who are like us.”
她表示：“人生路上，随着我们经历不同的阶段、年岁渐长，注意力会发生转移，我们会更愿意和与自己志同道合的人相处。”
So, changing friends is normal, but we still need those special pals who’ve known us long term.
所以，朋友的更迭是很正常的事，但我们依然需要那些相识多年的挚友。
These are friendships we invest time in.
这类友谊是我们倾注了时间去经营的。
According to Robin Dunbar, a professor of evolutionary psychology at the University of Oxford, these are your inner circle of friends – your “shoulders to cry on” – and you have to see them at least once a week to keep them in that circle.
牛津大学进化心理学教授罗宾·邓巴表示，这些人是你核心朋友圈里的人——是你“值得倾诉的对象”，想要维系这份情谊，你至少每周要和他们见一次面。
He adds that the friends that do drift are mostly “friendships of convenience”.
他还补充道，那些渐渐疏远的朋友，大多只是“利益之交”。
But the advice for maintaining a good friendship is to share how you feel with someone you trust – this can help strengthen your friendship as well as giving you both a chance to support each other.
而维系一段真挚友谊的秘诀，就是向你信任的人倾诉心声——这不仅能巩固你们的友谊，也能让彼此都有机会互相扶持。